				<Song song="Shadows and Stardust">
						<song_id>7</song_id>
						<Tone>Adventurous, Discover</Tone>
						<Plot>Venturing into the cosmos, Anya and her companions explore ancient ruins that whisper secrets of the universe's creation. Surrounded by celestial beings, they uncover the origins of the darkness threatening their existence. Each encounter reveals the fragility of light against encroaching shadows. Amidst breathtaking starfields and swirling galaxies, Anya contemplates her place within this grand tapestry, realizing that her actions could tip the balance between hope and despair. Meanwhile, Seraphina reflects on her role as a leader and her connection to the cosmos, understanding that her past losses are part of a larger story that can inspire others to rise against darkness.
						</Plot>
						<Lyrics>[Verse 1]
	In the twilight of existence, where the shadows softly creep,
	Lies a realm of ancient wonders, where the stardust dreams still sleep.
	Through the cosmic waves we travel, to a place where time stands still,
	In the heart of endless nightfall, where the stars bend to our will.

	[Pre-Chorus]
	In the silence of the galaxies, where the echoes start to fade,
	We find the strength within us, through the memories we've made.

	[Chorus]
	In the land of Shadows and Stardust, where the night and light collide,
	We’ll forge our paths in the darkness, through the memories we've made..
	Through the veil of endless mystery, where the dreams and echoes blend,
	In the land of Shadows and Stardust, our journey never ends.

	[Verse 2]
	From the depths of ancient whispers, to the heights of astral planes,
	We uncover hidden treasures, where the eternal knowledge reigns.
	With the courage of explorers, and the wisdom of the stars,
	We journey through the darkness, to where the cosmic secrets are.

	[Pre-Chorus]
	In the silence of the galaxies, where the echoes start to fade,
	We find the strength within us, through the memories we've made.

	[Chorus]
	In the land of Shadows and Stardust, where the night and light collide,
	We’ll forge our paths in the darkness, through the memories we've made.
	Through the veil of endless mystery, where the dreams and echoes blend,
	In the land of Shadows and Stardust, our journey never ends.

	[Bridge]
	In the land of Shadows and Stardust, where the night and light collide,
	We’ll forge our paths in the darkness, with the stars as our guide.
	Through the veil of endless mystery, where the dreams and echoes blend,
	In the land of Shadows and Stardust, our journey never ends.

	[Verse 3]
	As the night unveils its magic, and the stars begin to soar,
	We’ll stand upon the threshold, where the shadows ask for more.
	In the dance of cosmic forces, our hearts will find their light,
	Through the Shadows and the Stardust, we’ll conquer endless night.

	[Outro]
	When the final stars have faded, and the shadows claim the sky,
	We’ll rise as one together, with stardust in our eyes.
	For in the land of Shadows and Stardust, our spirits will ascend,
	Eternal in the cosmos, where our dreams and journeys blend.</Lyrics>
						<analysis>...</analysis>
					</Song>